-=TLF字幕组=-
翻译：诺阿诺阿，驯鹿
翻译：现代孔融让榴莲，茶包泰迪
校对：诺阿诺阿
「佩小姐的奇幻城堡」
你是否感到过自己所做的都毫无意义
Do you ever feel like nothing you do matters?
就像在海滩上留下的脚印
You leave footprints on the beach,
第二天便消失不见
and tomorrow they're gone.
就像不断重复的一天又一天
Like it's just today over again.
人们说十几岁时
They say your teen years
就是要交朋友、尽情玩耍
are for making friends and having fun...
对我来说这样更糟
which made me feel even worse.
嗨，艾米，我是杰克
Hey, Amy. It's Jake.
咱俩数学课一起上
I'm in your math class.
嘿，别忘了给自己买成人纸尿裤
Hey, don't forget your adult diapers.
呵呵
Yeah, right.
杰克，有电话找你
Jake. Phone for you.
但那一天开始，一切都变了
But that day, everything changed.
谢谢你送我，雪莉
Thanks for the ride, Shelley.
怎么让你去照顾你爷爷呢？
So, how come you have to go deal with your grandpa?
我爸他工作忙，走不开
My dad couldn't get out of work.
他还有工作？
I didn't think he worked.
我还是给爷爷打个电话吧
I'm just gonna call Grandpa.
我是亚伯
Hello, this is Abe.
我是杰克
Hey, it's Jake.
别过来！听我说
No! Don't come here. Listen to me.
这里不安全
It's not safe.
千万别来
Stay away.
爷爷，你今天吃药了吗？
Grandpa, did you take your pills today?
放枪的橱柜的钥匙，本来在抽屉里
The key to my gun cabinet, it was in the drawer.
现在不见了！
And now it's gone.
我爸拿走了，你不记得了？
Yeah, Dad took it, all right?
安全起见，好吧
For safekeeping. It's okay.
你爸拿走了？没有枪我怎么对付他们？
Your father wants I should fight them without a gun?
上帝保佑他
God bless him.
他是怎么了？老年痴呆？
What's his deal, Alzheimer's?
智力衰弱
Dementia.
那家伙吓我一跳
That guy gave me the heebie-jeebies.
有什么事就喊我
Holler if you need me.
爷爷？
Grandpa?
雪莉！
Shelley!
怎么回事？
What's goin' on?
有人闯进来了
Someone broke in.
我车里有枪，在这儿等我
I've got a.38 in my car. You wait there.
爷爷！
Grandpa!
911，您遇到了什么紧急情况？
911. What's your emergency?
我需要医务人员
911? Yeah, I need the paramedics.
地址是棕榈环路2040号，我爷爷…
It's at 2040 Palm Circle. My grandpa...
您遇到了什么紧急情况？
Sir, what's your emergency?
爷爷
Grandpa.
你得赶快走
You have to get away from here.
能听见我说话吗，先生？
Sir, can you hear me?
听我说
Please. Listen.
去岛上
Go to the island.
先生，医务人员正在赶来
Sir, paramedics are on their way.
找到艾默生
Find Emerson.
那张明信片
The postcard.
找到圈
Go to the loop.
1943年9月3号
September 3rd, 1943.
没事的
It's okay.
不要动，救护车马上来了
Just don't move. There's an ambulance coming.
你肯定觉得我疯了
I know you think I'm crazy.
但鸟会跟你解释的
But the bird will explain everything.
答应我，小老虎，你一定去
Will you do this, Tygrysku? Promise me?
我一定去
I promise, yes.
我以为自己能保护你
I thought I could protect you.
我早就应该告诉你
I should have told you years ago.
爷爷！告诉我什么？
Grandpa. Tell me what?
爷爷！
Grandpa!
雪莉，小心后面
Shelley, behind you!
那里没有人
There was no one there.
听我说，杰克…
May I say, Jake...
鉴于才过去一个月
that considering this was only a month ago...
我认为你的表现已经很好了
I think you're doing exceptionally well.
你是说不疯了？
Apart from being crazy?
做恶梦和焦虑并不代表你疯了
Having nightmares and anxiety doesn't make you crazy.
那看到并不存在的东西呢？
What about seeing things which aren't there?
在某些特殊情况下
Actually, in traumatic situations,
这种现象也很常见
it's not at all uncommon.
你头脑中的潜意识会提取电影中的画面，或是…
Your subconscious mind drew an image from a movie or...
是因为一个故事
It was a story.
我小时候，爷爷会给我讲故事
My grandpa told me stories when I was a kid...
讲他在战争中遇到的那些怪物
about monsters that he fought in the war.
你看
So there you go.
他当时伤的很重
He was brutally attacked...
所以你认为伤他的是非人类，是怪物
and in your head, the man who did it was inhuman, a monster.
不过也不是人
It wasn't a man, though.
警察说纱门上
The cops said that dogs
有狗抓过的痕迹
scratched up the screen door...
他追到树林里
and he chased them off into the woods.
验尸官说他当时心脏病发作
And the coroner said he had a heart attack.
警察说
And the cops said...
狗会吃掉尸体软组织
that dogs go for the soft parts.
他们检查了叉子上提取到的DNA
They DNA tested the fork...
里面有动物的DNA
and it had animal DNA.
就这么结案了
So, that's case closed.
听你说的，你爷爷应该是个了不起的人
He sounds like an extraordinary gentleman.
你俩很亲近吗？
Were you very close?
波多黎各
Puerto Rico.
这里
Here.
那里有个湖，湖水晚上会发光
There's a lake where the water glows in the dark.
还有一个秘密通道
And a secret tunnel.
我藏在里面躲过了怪物
That's where I hid from the monsters.
我小时候他经常照顾我
He used to babysit me a lot.
跟他在一起的时候，我有种特别的感觉
When I was with him, I felt special.
我的鸭子又干了
My duck was dry again.
亚伯，都11点了，他怎么还没睡
Abe. It's, like, 11:00. What is he doing up?
我要当一个探险家
I'm gonna be an explorer.
爷爷在帮我计划第一次航行
Grandpa's helping me plan my first voyage.
世上的角角落落都已经被探过了
Everything's already been discovered, buddy.
他们恐吓彼此
They terrorize each other...
然后大肆破坏，毁掉了岛上的其他地方
before wreaking havoc on the rest of the island.
别理你爸爸
Pay no attention to your father.
他什么都不知道
He knows bubkes.
走吧，小老虎，该睡了
Come, Tygrysku. Off to bed.
给我讲个故事吧
Can you tell me a story?
经常讲的那个？
The usual?
很久很久以前
Okay. Once upon a time...
有一个小男孩
there was a little boy...
要带图片
With the pictures.
图片啊
Pictures.
很久很久以前
Once upon a time...
有个小男孩名叫亚伯
there was a little boy called Abe.
就是你嘛
That was you.
是我
That was me.
他住在一个很美丽的福利院
And he lived in a lovely children's home
就在威尔士附近一座小岛上
on a little island near Wales...
那里每天都阳光灿烂
where the sun shone every day.
那里的女校长叫佩瑞格林小姐
The headmistress, Miss Peregrine...
她非常非常聪明
was very clever.
她还抽烟斗
And she smoked a pipe.
她还能变成鸟
She could turn into a bird.
那里是特殊儿童之家
It was a home for special children...
比如布朗温，还有维克多
like Bronwyn and Victor.
他俩都非常强壮，比得过十个壮汉
They were both as strong as 10 men.
还有休
And Hugh...
休身体住着蜜蜂
Hugh had bees living inside him.
艾玛呢？
Where's Emma?
她会飘起来
She could float.
她比空气还轻
She was lighter than air.
必须得穿上铅做的鞋子
She had to wear special shoes made of lead
否则会飘走
to keep her from floating away.
她现在在哪里？
Where is she now?
应该还在岛上吧
She's still on the island, I believe.
我的爸爸妈妈把我送到那里
My mama and papa sent me there...
和特殊的小孩子们一起生活
to live with the special children.
小老虎该睡觉了
And now, Tygrysku, time for sleep.
他总是叫我小老虎
He used to call me Tygrysku.
就是波兰语的小老虎的意思
It's Polish for "little tiger."
一点都不像我
He couldn't have picked a less appropriate nickname.
我那时候胆子很小
I was always a chicken.
你的爸爸妈妈为什么把你送走
Why did your mom and dad send you away?
我们那时住在波兰，那里不安全
Well, where we lived in Poland, it wasn't safe.
那里有怪物
There were monsters.
哪种怪物？
What kind of monsters?
超级大的怪物，有很长的手臂
Huge ones, with long arms...
没有眼睛
and no eyes...
触手就像这样
and tentacles like this.
可笑的是
The dumb thing was...
好多年，我都相信他的故事
for years, I actually believed his stories.
这个是米勒德，他是隐形人
And this is Millard. He's invisible.
老师说那些照片是专门唬人的
My teacher says they were trick photos.
你相信她说的吗？
And did you believe her?
爸爸说你大概是在某家
Dad says you probably found them
旧货商店找到的
at a junk store someplace...
就在你旅行的时候
when you went traveling.
我永远不会骗你，小老虎
I would never lie to you, Tygrysku.
但是你就是骗我了，福利院，还有怪物
But you did, about the home, the monsters.
爸爸说
Dad told me.
你爸爸知道
Your father knows very well
我小时候住在儿童之家
I went to live in the children's home.
他说那时候波兰的确有怪物
He said there really were monsters in Poland...
但不是长触角的那种怪物
just not the kind with tentacles.
他说你被送去威尔士是因为波兰有坏人
He said you got sent to Wales 'cause there were bad people.
那些人会杀掉所有跟他们不一样的人
People who wanted to kill anyone who was different.
我不想继续谈这个了
I don't wanna talk about this anymore.
他说那里的孩子是很特殊
He said the children were special...
但不是你说的那种特殊
but not the way you said.
发现什么好东西了？
You find something good?
哦，快瞧瞧，真棒
Oh, look at that. That's awesome.
带走吧
You should take that.
走吧，小伙子
Come on, buddy, let's roll.
你怎么跟没事儿人一样？
How are you so okay?
杰克，你跟爷爷的关系比我跟他亲近多了
Jakey, you were a lot closer to him than I ever was.
他是个好爷爷
He was a wonderful grandpa...
但不算是个好爸爸
but not such a great dad.
他所有的工作
Never seemed to pick a job...
都早出晚归
that didn't involve late nights
还经常出差很久
or long trips away, though.
我和你苏希姑姑
Me and Aunt Susie always kind of thought
都以为他出轨了
he was, maybe, cheating on our mom.
对不起，我知道你很崇拜爷爷
I'm sorry, buddy. I know how much you worshiped him...
但事实就是这样
but there it is.
惊喜吧！！
Surprise!
生日快乐，杰克表哥
Happy birthday, Cousin Jake!
杰克，真高兴
J-dog, it's great you're coming
你暑假和我们一起过
to spend a summer with us.
等会儿带你去看新船
Wait till you see the new boat.
很期待呢
Can't wait.
是苏希姑姑
It's Aunt Susie.
我猜这个礼物你会喜欢
Thought you might wanna open this one.
是爷爷送你的
It's from your grandpa.
我看到的时候已经包好了
Found it while I was packing up.
我猜他是想给你的
I figured he meant to give it to you someday.
谢谢姑姑
Thanks.
致杰克，以及他即将发现的世界
To Jake, and the worlds he has yet to discover.
最最亲爱的亚伯
My dearest Abe...
希望你能收到这张卡片
I hope this card finds you well.
孩子们和我都非常想你
The children and I yearn to hear your news.
希望你很快能再来看望我们
I do hope you will visit us again soon.
我们都非常期待见到你
We should so love to see you.
此致
With admiration...
阿尔玛·佩瑞格林
Alma Peregrine.
呃…两年前寄来的
H mm. Only two years ago.
很可能她还活着
I suppose it's possible she could still be alive.
对
Right.
我可以见见她
I could meet her.
也许能发现
Maybe even find out what it was
爷爷想让我知道的事情
Grandpa wanted me to know.
但是如果她死了呢？
But what if she's dead?
格兰医生
Dr. Golan...
我们很关心
we are very concerned
杰克现在的心理状况
with Jake's state of mind right now.
我没法放下工作
There's no way I'm putting my life on hold
带你去威尔士啊
to take you to Wales.
爸爸可以带我去
Dad could take me.
他可以去看鸟…
And he can look at birds...
顺便完成他的书
and work on his book.
你也能休息一段时间
It means you get a break.
就像格兰医生说的
As Dr. Golan said...
也许我就能放下了
maybe I can move on.
就像一种了结
Like, closure.
有机会去看看这个福利院
Having an opportunity to see this children's home...
将现实和幻想分离开
and separate fantasy from reality...
也许会有用
may be helpful.
至少
And at the very least...
这样一次旅行能让杰克有机会
a trip like this provides a chance to...
说再见
say goodbye.
“卡瑞霍姆，人口92人
"Cairnholm. Population of 92.
“因其最接近
"Best known for its proximity...
“奥古斯塔号邮轮最后的安息地而为人所知
"to the final resting place of the cruise liner Augusta...
“奥古斯塔号于1915年沉没
"which sank in 1915.
“岛上只有一家旅馆”
"There is just one hotel..."
只能住那儿了
That's us.
希望那里有波本酒
Yeah. I hope there's bourbon.
杰克！快看
Jake, check it out.
是只游隼
That's a peregrine falcon.
游隼，和那个女校长的名字一样
A peregrine, like the headmistress?
是啊
Sure.
说不定这就是为什么爷爷提到
That's probably where Grandpa came up
变成鸟的事情
with that whole turning into a bird thing.
说不定那真的是她
Or maybe, maybe that's really her!
佩小姐！
Hey, Miss Peregrine.
我是杰克
It's me, Jake.
亚伯·波特曼的孙子
I'm Abe Portman's grandson.
拜托别在我们头上拉便便
Please don't crap on us.
爸，我开玩笑呢！
Oh, my God. Dad, I'm kidding.
这…有人吗？
What the... Hello?
有人吗？
Hello?
有人在吗？
Anybody home?
你好
Oh, hey.
你知道这里的经理在哪儿吗？
Any idea where I'd find the manager of this place?
是我，抱歉久等了
That's me. Sorry to keep you.
刚带奥吉叔去上厕所了
Just helping Uncle Oggie to the loo.
我是凯文，楼上有房间
I'm Kev. There's room upstairs.
太好了
Oh, great.
我很快回来
I'll be back in a bit.
凯文去帮我们准备房间了
Kev's just getting our suite ready.
还要等一会儿
Um, while we're waiting...
要不咱们去海滩看看？
I thought maybe we could go check out the beach.
我还以为咱们要去儿童福利院呢
I thought we would go to the children's home.
那些鸟是在海滩上筑巢吗？
Is the beach where the birds nest?
我们…可以很快看一眼
I thought we could just check it out real quick.
我可以自己去福利院
I could go to the home by myself.
你就不用太匆忙了
Then, you can really take your time and enjoy it.
别这样，小杰，你妈知道了肯定会抓狂的
Come on, Jakey. You know your mom would freak.
要不找个人带我去吧
What if we can find someone to take me?
嗨，各位
Hey, dudes.
- 爸！别！
- 别吵
- Dad. Don't.
- Shh! I got this.
你们谁
I was just wondering if any of you guys...
有兴趣带我儿子
might be interested in taking my son here
去岛的另一边吗？
to the other side of the island.
你俩叫什么啊？
So, what are your names?
我是虫子，他是D哥
I'm Worm. This is MC Dirty D.
坏小子D哥
MC Dirty Bizniz.
我还以为你改了？
I thought you changed it.
没有
No.
你不记得了？
No, you did, remember?
露丝说坏小子D哥
When Ruth said "MC Dirty Bizniz"
听起来好像你裤子破了似的
made it sound like you cacked your trousers.
对，但她说这个名字听起来
Yeah, but she said "Dirty D" sounded like
好像个人卫生有问题
a personal hygiene problem.
听起来像是外号…
Wait. Are these, like, nicknames, or...
是艺名，我俩是威尔士最屌的说唱歌手
Stage names. We're the sickest rappers in Wales.
快，虫子，给美国佬露两手
Go on, Worm. Show this Yank how it's done.
现在？
What? Now?
我要把教堂搅个地覆天翻
I like to get wrecked down the Priest Hole
因为你爸去教堂领救济的钱
Your dad's always here 'cause he's on the dole
我们的韵脚最屌但听起来好像不难
Our rhymes are tight Yet I make it look easy
我们的节奏最炫好像火爆的咖喱饭
Our beats are hot like chicken jalfrezi
挺好的
Oh, yeah, no. It's good.
咱们抄小道吧，D哥
Should we take the shortcut, D?
这样快一点，从这儿走
We'll get there quicker. Take it from me.
这里下去？
What, down here?
去吧
Go.
这边？
This way?
这…
What the...
这是去福利院的路吗？
Is this even the way to the children's home?
要穿过那片林子
Right through those trees.
鞋丢了就丢了吧，孩子
No use crying over a lost shoe, boy-o.
那个福利院…发生了什么事？
The children's home. What happened to it?
德军空袭，炸弹正好落到福利院屋顶
A German air raid. Bomb fell right on the roof.
1943年9月3号
September the 3rd, 1943.
那…之后那些孩子呢？
Where did they go after?
女校长和孩子们呢？
The headmistress and the children.
无人生还，可怜的小东西们
Not one survivor. Poor little buggers.
都还那么可爱
And they were lovely, too.
为什么爷爷不告诉我们他们都死了？
Why didn't he tell us that they all died?
他离家去参军，三个月后
He leaves to join the army, and 3 months later,
他认识的人都死了
everyone he knows gets killed?
就算是爷爷也没法把这编成晚安故事啊
Not even Grandpa could turn that into a bedtime story.
也难怪他害怕做爸爸
Well, no wonder he was scared of being a dad...
和别人亲近
being close to anyone.
听我说
Listen.
你应该找人谈谈这件事
You need to talk about all this with someone, buddy.
我们可以给格兰医生打电话
We should call Dr. Golan.
真是个好天气
Certainly some enjoyment today.
我可以跟
Er, do you mind if I go hang out
其他孩子一起玩吗？
with those other kids today?
他们叫我一起玩
They asked.
当然了，很棒啊
Yeah? That's awesome.
亚伯？
Abe?
不！
No!
你是艾玛
You're Emma!
还有双胞胎
And the twins.
奥利弗
And Olive.
布朗温
And Bronwyn.
他是米拉德
And he's Millard.
不对啊，你死了
No, you're dead.
你们都死了
All of you, you're all dead.
他虽然能隐形，但是也死了
He's invisible, but he's still dead.
我们都没死
None of us are dead.
天呐，难道是我死了？
Oh, my God. Am I dead?
不是
No.
刚才在里面
You called me Abe.
你为什么叫我亚伯？
In the house. Why?
你跟他很像
You looked like him.
一瞬间很像而已
Just for a moment,
后来你就又喊又叫
before you started screaming...
跑掉了，还撞到了脑袋
running away, and concussing yourself.
这是怎么回事？
Wait. What's happening?
我们在等天黑
We're waiting until the coast is clear...
然后去圈里
before we go into the loop.
隔墙有耳，不可不防
You never know who might be watching.
你刚说去哪里
Wait. Before we go into what?
快走吧，杰克
Please, Jake.
佩小姐在等你，她看见你们的船了
Miss Peregrine's waiting. She saw you on the ferry.
她派我们来接你
She sent us to get you.
嘿！
Hey!
你准备去哪里啊？
Where do you think you're going?
回房间啊
To my room.
我是这里的住客
I'm a guest here.
你看这像旅馆吗？
Does this look like a hotel to you?
对啊
Yeah.
我有钥匙
No. I've got a key.
你问问经理，他知道
Talk to the manager. He'll tell you.
我就是经理
I'm the manager, boy.
他是美国人，可能是军人
He's American. Maybe he's army?
胡说
Bollocks.
听他的口音，真难听
Listen to his accent. It's terrible.
他是个间谍
He's a spy.
什么？
What?
我不是，我是游客
No, I'm not. I'm a tourist.
要我说，我们让他说实话
I say we should get the truth out of him
按老规矩来
the old-fashioned way.
快走！
Come on!
杰克，快上来！
Jake, get on!
快点！
Come on! Get on, boy!
原来你们都是真的！
I can't believe you're real. You're all real!
不是一直在告诉你嘛
We have been trying to tell you.
但是原来我也很特殊
But I'm special, too.
什么？
What?
刚才在酒馆啊，奥利芙看见了
in the pub. Olive, you saw.
那些东西飞来飞去的
Right? Everything was flying and breaking.
是我干的
And that was me!
用意念
I was doing it with my mind.
是我干的
No, that was me.
米拉德？
Millard?
对啊
Yeah.
你没穿衣服？
Are you naked?
对啊
Yeah.
哦
Oh.
我不…
I don't...
1943年一颗炸弹落在你们头顶
A bomb dropped on you in 1943.
现在就是1943年
It is 1943.
1943年9月3日
September the 3rd, 1943.
每一天，这一天
All day, every day.
就是我们的圈
It's our loop.
分秒不差
Right on time.
我是佩小姐，幸会幸会
Miss Peregrine. Delighted to meet you.
希望酒馆老板不会再
I do hope I'm not going to have the pub landlord
带着警察找上门来了
knocking on my door with the police again.
这个月已经杀过他们两次了
I've had to kill them twice this month.
太不方便了
It's been terribly inconvenient.
米拉德打破了几件东西，再没了
Millard broke a few things. That's all.
还有奥利芙好像放了点火
And Olive may have started a tiny fire.
但是他们要伤害杰克的
But they were going to hurt Jake.
瞧瞧你
Look at you.
亚伯上一次寄给我的照片上
The last time dear Abe sent me a photograph...
你还是个小宝宝呢
you were just a tiny tot.
别站着了，快进来吧
Don't just stand there. Come in.
茶都要凉了
Your tea's getting cold.
你怎么知道酒馆的事？
How did you know about the pub?
你体重大概109磅，对吧？
You weigh approximately 109 pounds, correct?
我不…
I don't...
你跑掉后6分钟布朗温和双胞胎就回来了
Bronwyn and the twins returned 6 minutes after you ran away.
我可能漏掉了什么
I think I'm missing something.
你觉得酒馆是安全的
And quite apart from the fact
所以最可能的情况就是你
that the perceived safety of the pub...
一路跑回了酒馆
makes it the most likely place to which you would flee...
跑回酒馆要花18分钟时间
it would take you 18 minutes to run there.
艾玛和米拉德坐马车过去
Emma and Millard would have been moments behind...
会稍晚一点
on the horse and trap,
他们的速度是8.2英里每小时
traveling at 8.2 miles per hour.
考虑到酒馆里发生的混乱
Factoring in some sort of kerfuffle at the pub...
和返程中增加了你的重量
and the return journey with your added weight...
你们会在4点过13分准时到达
you would arrive here at 13 minutes past 4.
好了，你的茶要加糖吗？
Now, then, do you take sugar?
可以了，谢谢你，奥利芙
That'll do. Thank you, Olive.
茶太烫了可不好
Nobody enjoys over-boiled tea.
我来帮你吧，伊诺克
Let me help you with those, Enoch.
不麻烦了，我可不想搅了你们的雅兴
Don't bother. Wouldn't want to interrupt your tea party.
节哀顺变，杰克
I'm so sorry for your loss, Jake.
看来你知道了
You know, then.
我知道如果亚伯活着
I know if Abe were alive,
一定会通知我们你要来
he would have told me you were coming.
我们到外面喝茶吧
Shall we take our tea outside?
谢谢
Thank you.
他死之前，让我找到你
Before he died, he told me to find you.
有些事他想让我知道
There was something he wanted me to know.
他说你会向我解释所有事
He said you could explain everything.
确实如此
That's absolutely true.
少有我解释不了的事情
There are very few things I can't explain.
我们就是通用语中所说的
We're what's known, in common parlance,
“异能”
as "peculiar."
晚了51秒，菲奥娜
51 seconds late, Fiona.
对不起，佩小姐
Sorry, Miss Peregrine.
晚餐需要准备多少胡萝卜？
How many carrots do you need for supper?
一颗就够了
Just one will do.
刚才说到，有些人拥有异能
As I was saying, some people are peculiar.
是家族中遗传下来的隐性基因
It's a recessive gene carried down through families.
然而，很多家庭的很多代人中
Yet, many generations can pass
都很难出现一个异能的孩子
without a peculiar child being born.
因此，异能人很多年来一直受到迫害
And alas, peculiars have been persecuted through the ages.
所以我能才生活在这样的地方
Hence, we live in places like this.
威尔士？
In Wales?
只要选对了日子，哪里都是一样
Anywhere will do if you pick the right day.
这就可以了，菲奥娜
That's fine now, Fiona.
我的异能是我是只回时鸟
You see, I'm a type of peculiar called an Ymbryne.
也就是说我可以
That means I can...
对，你可以变成鸟
Yeah, you turn into a bird.
话是没错
I do. Yes.
不过这没多大用处
But that's not very useful.
回时鸟的主要能力是可以操控时间
An Ymbryne's main skill is the manipulation of time.
我们挑个安全的日子，安全的地点
We choose a safe place, a safe day...
然后创造圈
and create a loop.
这是什么意思？
What do you mean?
一个时间圈可以保持24小时
A loop preserves the last 24 hours.
重置时间圈，就可以重新生活这一天
Reset the loop, and the day is yours to live in again.
每天重置
Reset it daily...
就可以永远停留
and you can stay there forever.
与世隔绝，保证安全
Entirely safe from the outside world.
刚刚好，布朗温，好姑娘
Right on time, Bronwyn. Good girl.
所以总是由回时鸟
And that's why we Ymbrynes
来照顾孩子们
are charged with the care of the young.
没有人会老去
And no one ever gets older.
这是最好的方法
It's best for everyone this way.
我向你保证
I assure you.
每一只回时鸟都会…
Every Ymbryne commits herself...
创造和守护一个这样的地方
to the creation and upkeep of a place like this.
这是异能孩子的家园
A home for peculiar children.
你已经见过双胞胎了
You met the twins.
这是克莱尔
This is Claire.
你也见过米拉德了
Millard you met.
那是休
And that's Hugh.
休，不要作弊
Stop cheating, Hugh.
米勒，你又犯规了！
Millard, that's a foul again.
才不是！裁判？
No, it wasn't. Ref?
如果你们玩的时候非要吵架
If you two can't play soccer without squabbling...
那就最好不要玩
I do wish you wouldn't play at all.
你知道裁判是干什么的吗？
Do you know what a referee is?
下午好，我是霍勒斯
Good afternoon. I'm Horace.
很高兴见到你
Delighted to meet you.
我们急需新鲜血液的注入
We sorely need some new blood here.
衬衣不错
Super shirt, by the way.
谢了
Thanks.
你肯定知道艾玛
You know Emma, of course.
差不多人都认齐了
And I think that's everyone.
布朗温是不是有个兄弟？
Didn't Bronwyn have a brother?
对，维克多在楼上
Yes. Victor's upstairs.
等等，伊诺克和奥莉芙去哪儿了？
Wait, where did Enoch and Olive go?
鬼知道
Heaven knows.
从我们去找杰克时，伊诺克就不见了
Enoch's been off sulking ever since we went out to get Jake.
佩小姐，有个警察在敲门
Miss Peregrine, there's a policeman at the door.
他说来处理酒馆的事
He says it's about the pub!
我们等会再谈这事，艾玛
We'll discuss this later, Emma.
不是他们的错
It wasn't their fault.
真的，他们只是想要帮我
Honestly, they were just trying to help.
谢谢
Thanks.
你没我想的那么傻
You're not as wet as I thought.
她不会杀人的，对吧？
She's not really gonna kill anyone, is she?
只要她能说服那个人
Not if she can talk her way out of it.
帮我个忙吧
Would you help me with something?
通常都是伊诺克干的
Enoch usually does it, but like I said,
不过他现在应该在哪儿生闷气呢
he's off sulking somewhere.
是因为我吗？
Is that because of me?
他占有欲很强
He's possessive.
所以…你要我帮你什么？
So, what did you need help with?
我的一项日常工作
One of my daily chores.
把松鼠宝宝送回树上
Put the baby squirrel back in the tree.
什么松鼠宝宝？
What baby squirrel?
每天都会发生？
That happens every day?
分秒不差
Like clockwork.
能帮我把绳子拴在腰上吗？
Now, would you mind tying that rope around my waist?
一定要抓紧绳子啊
Right. Promise to hold on tight.
差点搞砸了
I nearly messed that up.
亚伯也是…第一次的时候
Abe did, too, the first time.
这以前是他的工作
This used to be his job.
艾玛，我得告诉你件事
Emma, I need to tell you something.
他死了
He's dead.
我知道
I know.
佩小姐猜到了，她总是对的
Miss Peregrine guessed, and she's always right.
没事的
It's okay.
我很久以前就和他说过再见了
I said goodbye to him a long time ago.
你们很亲近是吗？
Were you close?
我以为是
I thought we were.
一度
For a while.
但我觉得应该不是
But I suppose not.
容我问一句，他喜欢你，对吧？
Can I ask, was he like you?
他很像你，杰克
He was like you, Jake.
我要去换件衣服，准备吃晚餐了
I need to go and change for supper.
你会和我们一起用餐吗？
Will you be dining with us?
我不能在外面待太晚
I can't stay out late.
晚餐五点半开始
Supper's at 5:30.
那…挺早的
Uh... That is pretty early.
幸好我们不都是八岁的孩子
The fact we're not all eight years old
给佩小姐减少了不少负担
seems to have eluded Miss Peregrine.
你可以借件亚伯的衣服穿
You can borrow some of Abe's clothes.
他的房间在阁楼
His room's in the attic.
杰克
Jake!
来认识认识伊诺克
Come and meet Enoch properly.
你应该不太适应这里的环境
You must feel pretty out of place.
不用担心
Don't worry.
我习惯了
I'm used to it.
我不担心
No. I wasn't worried.
但还是给你一些忠告，开诚布公的讲
Some advice for you though, man to man.
如果你只是因为喜欢艾玛才待在这里
If you're thinking of staying just because you like Emma...
就不必了
don't bother.
她心碎以后
You see, she swore off romance decades ago...
已经多年不沾情爱了
when she got her heart broken.
她也不会改变想法的
And she's never gonna change her mind. So...
伊诺克，我不是…
Enoch, I wasn't...
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
是不是很棒？
Isn't he amazing?
你刚才做的是什么？
What did you do?
这个？
This?
杰克，这还不是最有趣的
Jake, this isn't even the fun part.
你想看最有趣的吗？
Do you want to see the fun part?
它们就像傀儡
They're like puppets.
听我的命令
Just do anything I tell them.
如果是人的话就更有趣了
It's even more fun with people.
你该看看我以前参与的
You should have seen some of
史诗级的战争
the epic battles they used to have...
发生在我父母的葬礼上
at my parents' funeral parlor.
你还需要领结
You'll need a necktie.
我祖父在旅行期间，做了什么？
So what did my grandpa do when he was traveling?
参观其他的时间圈
Visited other loops.
是吗？做什么？
Really? To do what?
杰克，有些问题
Jake, there's some questions
我不能回答你的，好吗？
that I can't answer, all right?
所以你最好还是
So, it would be a lot easier for me if you just...
不要问了
stopped asking them.
你在干什么？
Hey! What are you doing?
米拉德
Millard.
去穿件衣服
Go and put some clothes on.
懂礼貌的人不会吃晚餐的时候不穿衣服
Polite persons do not take their supper in the nude.
好吧！
All right. All right.
杰克你可以坐这里
You can sit here, Jake.
瞧瞧伊诺克
Look at Enoch.
他又嫉妒了
He's jealous.
我嫉妒什么？
Why would I be jealous?
你们想结婚就结好了，与我无关
Olive can go marry Jake, for all I care.
伊诺克，别这样，她没这样想
Don't be mean, Enoch. She doesn't want to.
她只是因为有访客而激动罢了
She's just excited to have a visitor.
没人要结婚
Nobody is marrying anybody.
现在大家快吃饭，别等菜凉了
Now, eat up your food before it gets cold.
休
Hugh!
你的网罩呢？
Where's your net?
休，别这样！
Hugh! You have to stop doing this, Hugh.
杰克，你一定觉得十分诡异吧
Must be very strange for you, Jake.
见到了你祖父的朋友
Meeting your grandfather's friends.
来到另一个世纪
Visiting another century.
你生活的时代有宇宙飞船吗？
Are there spaceships in your time, Jake?
像飞侠哥顿里的一样
Like the Flash Gordon books.
好了！奥莉芙
Now, now, Olive.
我以前说过什么
What did I say about asking questions?
我们不讨论将来
We don't discuss the future here.
只活在当下，享受一切
We enjoy living in the good old here and now.
克莱尔，你怎么不吃?
Claire, why aren't you eating?
在杰克面前，她不太好意思
She's embarrassed in front of Jake.
没关系的
Don't be. Please.
杰克，你的异能是什么？
So, Jake, what's your peculiarity?
我…我没有异能
Oh, I'm not peculiar.
看到了吧
And that, my friends,
这就是他为什么不能和我们待在一起
is why he will not be staying with us...
不管我们怎么劝他
no matter how hard we try to persuade him.
我们已经说过这件事了，杰克只是来做客的
We've spoken about this. Jake is just visiting.
他也许想留下呢
He might want to stay.
你想待在这里吗，杰克？
Don't you want to stay, Jake?
今晚还是…
Tonight? Or...
永远，你应该永远留在这里
Forever. You should stay forever.
没必要的话为什么要留下来？
Why would he, if he doesn't have to?
他可以在外面生活，慢慢变老
He can live out there, grow older...
享受时光
have a good time instead.
然后像他祖父那样，离开人世
He'll leave, just like his grandfather did.
艾玛！
Emma!
抱歉
Excuse me.
她去哪里？
Where's she going?
伊诺克，这样很不好！
That wasn't nice, Enoch.
你明明知道亚伯离开我们
You know perfectly well why Abe left us.
是为了去参军
To join the army.
接着他遇到了一个姑娘，然后结了婚
And then he met a lady, and had a nice wedding cake...
还有个可爱的小宝宝
and a lovely little baby.
孩子们！
Children.
我知道你们都想认识新朋友
I know you'd all like a new friend...
但杰克在佛罗里达还有很多自己的事
but I'm sure Jake has plenty of his own back in Florida.
我希望在我接完电话后
I think you should all get ready
你们可以准备好去看电影了
for movie time while I answer that.
可是你总是让我们待在那里
But you always let us stay for it.
嗨，我是亚伯
Hello, this is Abe.
大家都还好吗？
How is everyone?
杰克，你的我多加了棉花糖糖
Yours has extra marshmallows, Jake.
米拉德，把睡衣穿上
Millard, put some pajamas on.
这里好热
It's too hot in here.
不要抱怨了
Stop moaning.
抱歉
Excuse me.
我祖父给我讲过
My grandpa told me about this.
霍勒斯能把他做的梦投放出来，是吗？
Horace projects his dreams, right?
他过去常听收音机
He used to listen to the radio.
极其乏味，我已经倒背如流了
Gets tedious when you know every word off by heart.
很好，这件我要了
Splendid. I'll take it.
很多都是关于服装的
He dreams about clothes mostly.
很高兴见到你
Delighted to meet you.
衬衫不错
Super shirt, by the way.
他什么时候梦到这个的？
When did he dream this?
昨晚
Last night.
有些梦有预见性
Some of his dreams are prophetic.
但绝大多数还是关于服装的
But, mostly they're about clothes.
预见性是说，他能预见未来？
Prophetic as in, he can see into the future?
回时鸟，她是谁？
An Ymbryne. Who is she?
佩小姐，你认识她吗？
Miss Peregrine, do you know her?
傻瓜
Don't be silly.
霍勒斯只是做了个噩梦而已
Horace must have just had a bad dream. That's all.
足够了，谢谢你，霍勒斯
That's quite enough of that. Thank you, Horace.
我想我该走了
I should probably get going.
你可以在这待一晚上，你愿意的话
You could stay the night, if you wanted to.
这样就不要晚上走回去了
Rather than walk home alone in the dark.
这座岛不是挺安全的吗？
But the island is very safe, isn't it?
当然
Of course!
我是说这里的路特别难走
I only meant the path is dreadfully bumpy.
杰克可能会跌倒
Jake could trip.
或许你可以带他走近路？
Perhaps you could show him the shortcuts.
这样他就不会跌倒了
Should he ever need to avoid bumps.
不留下来看看如何开始新的一天吗？
Won't you at least stay to see the reset, Jake?
超震撼的
It's really quite spectacular.
留下来吧，杰克！
Yeah! Stay, Jake!
什么声音？
What was that?
我的手机
It was my phone.
可能是在时间圈里，一直都没信号
It's been dead the whole time in the loop. I guess now...
你的手机？
Your phone?
对，就像电话
Yeah. Like a telephone.
可以打电话
You can call people...
可以发短信
send written messages.
对了，你会喜欢这个的
Wait, you'll love this.
你可以拍照
You can take a picture.
按那里…那…对
Press that, there. Yeah.
看见了没？
See?
怎么了？
What's wrong?
想到有一天你会长大
It's just funny to think that one day, you'll grow up.
就像亚伯
Like Abe did.
结婚生子
Get married, have children.
孙子孙女
Grandchildren.
你也许还会给他们看这张照片
You might even show them this photograph.
而我还在这里
And I'll still be here.
你能离开这里吗？
Couldn't you leave some day?
如果你想的话，能生活在现实世界吗？
And live in the present, if you wanted to?
不行
No.
在那里待几分钟
More than a few minutes in your time
时间就会赶上来
and the years would catch up.
你会变老？
You would age?
这个好像是霍勒斯梦中的回时鸟
I think it's the Ymbryne from Horace's dream.
你确定它不是一只普通的鸟吗？
Are you sure it's not just a bird?
我不知道，它难道不会变身吗？
I don't know, wouldn't it change?
不能，她受伤了
She can't. Not if she's hurt.
我要把她带进去，你该走了
I need to take her inside. You should go.
请不要说话了
Please don't say anything else.
我讨厌说再见
I hate goodbyes.
我明天再来
I'll come back tomorrow.
不用着急，我永远都在这里
There's no hurry. I'll be here forever.
嘿！
Hey!
我在这个破岛上转了一整天了
I've been all over this damn island.
你去哪儿了？
Where the hell were you?
我正好往回走
Um, I was just on my way back.
对不起，我忘了看时间了
I'm sorry. I lost track of time.
我和虫子，还有D哥玩儿了一天
I was having a blast with Worm and Dirty D.
D哥？
Dirty D?
你知道吗？
You know what?
我觉得这样挺好，很健康
This is good. This is healthy.
你认识了古怪的朋友
You're making weird friends...
跟其他年轻人们一样
and doing teenage stuff.
我觉得这挺好的
I think this is normal.
格兰医生肯定会同意这么做的
I'm sure Doctor Golan will approve.
嘿，那个美国佬
Hey, you. American!
到这儿来
Get over here.
哦，他们俩在那儿
Oh, look. There they are.
D哥和虫子
There's D-Bag and Worm Man.
是你干的吗？
Did you do this?
什么？不是！
What? No.
当然不是
Of course not.
肯定不是我们
It wasn't us.
这位先生，我不知道这里发生了什么
Listen, sir. I don't know what happened here.
但是我儿子一直和他朋友在一起
But my son and his friends have been together all day.
杰克肯定不会干这种事儿的
Jake would never do anything like this.
胡说！我们今天就没见过他！
Bollocks! We haven't seen him!
你昨天付了我们钱
You paid us yesterday.
我们今天为什么要免费陪他玩儿？
Why would we hang out with him today for free?
杰克，你今天有没有和他们在一起？
Jake? Were you with them or not?
没有！对不起！
No. I'm sorry.
你不是真的觉得这是我做的吧？
But you don't seriously think I could do this?
我想我们已经都弄清楚了
I think we're done here, sir.
能帮我留个言吗？
Can you pass on a message for me?
你就告诉格兰医生
Can you tell Doctor Golan...
要不是她怂恿进行这次荒谬的旅行
that if she hadn't encouraged this cockamamie trip...
我儿子也不会
maybe my son wouldn't be
跑到一个废弃的房子里面呆了一整天
moping around all day in a derelict house...
以至于都神情恍惚了！
having a goddamn breakdown!
喂？
Hello?
爸，我没有
Dad, I'm not.
我没事儿
I'm fine.
你不好
No. You're not.
你有事儿，杰克
You're not fine, Jake.
到这儿来就是个彻头彻尾的错误
Coming here was a terrible, terrible idea.
对不起，我说谎了
Look, I'm sorry I lied. I just wanted...
闹钟定在早上8点
Just set your alarm for 8:00 a.m.
我想早点儿去海滩上看看
I wanna get to the beach early.
剩下这几天
The rest of the time we're stuck
在这个破岛上
on this craphole island...
我们俩必须一起行动
we're sticking together.
你去哪儿？
Where are you going?
去楼下喝一杯
Downstairs for a drink.
亲爱的佩小姐
Dear Miss Peregrine...
我不想让你们担心
I don't wish to alarm you...
但是我的一个线人告诉我
but one of my informants sent me this.
巴伦先生的一些同伙
It would appear that some of Mr. Barron's group...
出现在英格兰黑谭镇附近
are in Blackpool, England.
如果我没记错
If I recall...
艾娃塞小姐在那儿有一个时间圈
Miss Avocet has a loop there.
请给她发出预警
Please warn her and suggest...
让她尽快建立一个新的时空循环
that she make a new one right away...
隐匿好行踪
well-hidden.
请珍重
And take the greatest care yourself.
祝好，亚伯
With love, Abe.
2016年1月
January, 2016.
准备好去海滩了吗？
Who's ready to hit the beach?
我去…
Oh, my...
难以置信！
Unbelievable.
在鸟巢区域架设备？
Right in the middle of a nesting area?
哪儿来的外行居然这么干？
What kind of idiot does that?
事实上，主要筑巢区在那边
Actually, the main nesting area is over there.
你想看看吗，我可以领你过去
I can show you if you'd like.
很高兴能在此遇到一个同样喜欢拍摄鸟类的人
It's marvelous to meet a fellow bird spotter.
约翰·拉蒙特
John Lamont.
富兰克林·波特曼，这是我儿子，杰克
Franklin Portman. This is my son, Jake.
约翰·拉蒙特
John Lamont.
你居然带着这么棒的相机来这儿
That's a hell of a camera you got there.
谢谢，这地方真是太赞了
Oh, thanks. It's absolutely fantastic.
我是来给我的书拍一些插图的
I'm here to do some snaps for a book I'm writing.
你们二位是过来度假的吗？
So, you gentlemen here on holiday?
不幸的是，她的翅膀
Unfortunately, her wings were flapping
呼哒的就像一只鸟！
as much as the bird's!
我觉得你们
I think you fellas are
现在想的是另一种鸟
thinking of another kind of bird.
你今天不再去海滩照相了吗？
So, you're not going to the beach today?
有什么意义呢？
What's the point?
如果那个家伙举着相机
If that guy is gonna cover Cairnholm
把整个岛的照片都发表在他那个包装精美的书里
in some big, glossy book...
谁还会看我拍的照片
no one's gonna even wanna look at mine.
我去睡个午觉
Might just have a nice afternoon nap.
你俩今早在哪里
I don't suppose you saw Uncle Oggie
看见老欧吉了吗？
on your travels this morning, did you?
按说他现在应该过来了
He's usually here by now.
我可以帮忙去找找他
I could go look for him.
你哪儿也别想去
You're not going anywhere.
杰克，你回来了！快来和我们一起玩儿！
Jake, you're back! Come and play!
我想要先见见佩小姐
I need to see Miss Peregrine first.
你知道她在哪儿吗？
Do you know where she is?
杰克，你回来了，太好了！
Jake. You're back. How wonderful!
它怎么样了？
How's it doing?
艾玛说这是一只回时鸟
Emma said it was an Ymbryne.
她，不是“它”
"She." Not "it."
回时鸟都是女性
Ymbrynes are always female.
艾玛说的非常正确
And Emma was quite correct.
这位是艾娃塞小姐
This is Miss Avocet.
她的时间圈在英格兰黑谭镇
Her loop's in Blackpool. England.
这是私人信件，杰克
That was a private letter, Jake.
谁是巴伦先生？
Who is Mr. Barron?
佩小姐，如果我爷爷
Miss Peregrine, if my Grandpa
和什么危险的人物有瓜葛
was involved with dangerous people...
我有必要将这些都告诉给警察
I need to tell the police.
告诉警察？
Police?
你这是在暗示亚伯是非正常死亡吗？
Are you implying Abe died an unnatural death?
我在树林里找到他时
I found him in the woods...
他的眼睛不见了
with his eyes missing.
我觉得这很不正常
I'd say that was pretty unnatural.
除非必要，我不想讨论这些让人不愉快的事儿
Unless essential, I don't discuss unpleasant matters.
回时鸟的职责是保护孩子，杰克
An Ymbryne's duty is to protect children, Jake.
我不是小孩儿了
I'm not a child.
爷爷他想让你把这些都告诉我
He wanted you to tell me everything!
哦，真郁闷啊
Oh. How frustrating for you.
鉴于佩小姐的规定
Between Miss Peregrine's rules...
以及我那条不想吓坏你的室友守则
and my housemates' little pact not to scare you off...
所以，没有人会给你答案的
it's like no one's telling you anything!
要不你来告诉我？
Why don't you, then?
反正你也不想我留在这儿
It's not like you want me here.
伊诺克，你不能告诉他，你保证过不说的
Enoch, you can't. You promised.
奥利芙说得对
Olive's right.
但是我知道有一个人
I do know someone who can get away
可以不用遵守这项规定
with breaking rules though.
你想去见见他吗？
Want to meet him?
伊诺克，别这么做，求你了！
Enoch, don't do this. Please!
是你想大家一起玩的
You want to spend time with me and Jake,
我们可以一起玩
we can all play together.
自己说的话不记得了？
That's what you said.
就是这儿了
Here we all are.
让开，奥利芙
Move, Olive.
你要是非这么做
If you're going to be like that,
我以后就不跟你做朋友了
then I don't want to be your friend.
伊诺克！别打扰维克多，布朗温会不高兴的
Enoch, leave Victor alone. It really upsets Bronwyn.
别闹了，菲奥娜
Stop fussing, Fiona.
你不觉得杰克应该和这里的每个人都认识一下吗？
Don't you think Jake should meet everybody?
他想把你吓跑，杰克
He's trying to frighten you away, Jake.
他一直都嫉妒艾伯，现在他又开始嫉妒你
He was always jealous of Abe. And now he's jealous of you.
还是过来跟我们一起玩儿吧
Come and play with us instead.
我想我应该去见见维克多
I'd quite like to meet Victor.
你先请
After you.
你好维克多
Hello, Victor.
我是杰克，不好意思打扰你
I'm Jake. I'm sorry to disturb...
他听不见你说话
Yeah, he can't hear you.
你好杰克，我叫维克多
Hello, Jake. I'm Victor.
你想知道是什么杀害了我吗？
Do you want to know what killed me?
你在这儿呢，他没和你一起吗？
There you are. Is Enoch with you?
到了每天散步的时间了
It's time for our daily walk.
艾玛，是谁害了维克多？
Emma, who killed Victor?
是那些白色眼睛的人吗？
Was it the people with the white eyes?
我跟你说了别问这么多
I asked you not to ask questions.
我爷爷去世的那晚我见过一个
I saw one the night my grandpa died.
这样的人
A man.
如果你的确见过这么一个
If it really was one,
你应该告诉佩小姐
you have to tell Miss Peregrine.
你能从照片里认出这个人吗？
Could you recognize him from a photograph?
你有照片吗？
Do you have one?
那就跟我走，跟我去个地儿
Come on. There's somewhere I go to be alone.
我在那儿存了些东西
I have things there.
是这儿吗？
Is this the place?
不是，这只是我们去哪儿的途径
No. This is how we get there.
艾玛！你的鞋！
Oh! Emma! Your shoes!
铅鞋！
Lead shoes!
欢迎来到我的秘密基地
Welcome to my secret hideout.
你是，你是怎么？
How did you...
空气
Air.
这是我的能力
It's my peculiarity.
它可以帮我实现想法
It does what I want.
杰克
Jake...
你爷爷退隐前
before your grandfather retired...
让我保管这些
he asked me to keep this safe.
这些是我爷爷的旧地图
This is my grandpa's old map.
上面标记了时间圈的所在地
It shows you where the loops are.
就是他
That's him!
这就是我见过的那个人
That's the man I saw.
他是谁？这就是巴伦
Who is he? That's Barron.
他是领头人
He's the leader.
什么的领头人？
The leader of what?
这些人都是谁？
Who are these people?
坏人，坏的异能者
Bad people. Bad peculiars.
亚伯终其一生都在追捕这些人
Abe dedicated his life to hunting them down.
这些是他没有找到的
These are the ones he never found.
“追捕”是什么意思？
What do you mean, hunting?
他们会袭击时间圈
They raided loops.
残忍的杀害其中所有的孩子
Whole homes full of children left for dead.
亚伯只是以暴制暴
Abe took lives to save lives.
你出生后，为了保护你他就退隐了
He only retired when you were born to protect you.
保护我什么？
From what?
如果我告诉你全部
If I tell you the rest,
你要保证你不逃避
you have to promise not to run away.
杰克，你是属于这里的
Jake, you belong here.
你知道我不属于
You know I don't.
我和你不一样
I'm not like you.
我是个普通人
I'm just ordinary.
不，你不是
No, you're not.
杰克
Jake...
只有异能人才能进入时间圈
only a peculiar can enter a time loop.
不是，这不可能
No. That can't be right.
我是说，我要是异能人我应该知道
I would know.
好吧
Fine.
那么我就给你看看其他的
Then I'll show you something else.
快来！会赶不上的
Hurry. You'll miss it.
回时鸟通常会选择一个完美的日子去建立时间圈
Ymbrynes usually pick the perfect day to create a loop.
但是佩小姐是匆忙间选择的日子
But Miss Peregrine had to make this one in a rush.
为什么？
Why?
因为德国人会用炸弹摧毁我们的房子
Because the Germans were about to drop a bomb on the house.
问题是
The point is...
1943年9月3日不是个完美的日子
September the 3rd, 1943 wasn't perfect.
那个杀害了维克多的家伙那天又回来了
The thing that killed Victor came back.
等等，小心！
Wait! Watch out!
你会让她分心的！
You'll put her off!
你能看见，是不是？
You can see it, can't you?
没有人能看得见
No one else can.
他们是隐形的，杰克
It's invisible, Jake.
这就是亚伯的天赋
That was Abe's greatest gift of all.
他可以看见那些怪物
He could see the monsters.
我们管他们叫灵体变异人
We call them Hollowgast.
简称灵人
Hollows for short.
我爷爷跟我提过有变成怪物的人
My grandpa told me about people who turn into monsters.
就是他们吗？
Is that what they are?
我会详细跟你解释的，杰克
I will explain everything, Jake.
考虑到现在的情况，我恐怕没得选
I fear it's my duty now, considering.
但是你要知道
But you should know that in doing so,
我这么做的确破坏了我曾经发过的誓
I'm breaking a solemn promise.
你一出生我就知道你是异能人
I knew you were peculiar when you were born.
但是你爷爷让我什么都不要告诉你
But your grandfather forbid me to tell you anything.
他最大的愿望就是希望你能有一个正常的童年
His dearest wish was for you to have an ordinary childhood.
我的童年的确过得很平凡
I definitely had that.
他本来打算等你18岁之后再告诉你的
He intended to tell you the truth when you turned 18.
他希望那些睡前故事可以提前铺垫一下
He hoped his bedtime stories would pave the way.
这是我的书
Here's my book.
很多年前
Many years ago...
从我们的族群中分裂出了一批人
a splinter faction emerged among our people.
对于异能人只能存在于时间圈中非常不满意
Disaffected peculiars tired of living in loops.
这就是巴伦先生
That's Mr. Barron.
他认为按照他的方法
He believed that by harnessing the essence
提取回时鸟的能力
of an Ymbryne's powers...
他和他的同伙可以获得永生
he and his cronies could gain immortality...
而且不用困在时间圈里
and be able to live outside loops.
于是他就设计了一个试验
He devised an experiment.
他绑架了一只回时鸟
He kidnapped an Ymbryne...
在不顾那只回时鸟死活的情况下
not knowing or caring
开始了试验
whether she would survive the experiment.
但是巴伦和他的同伙
But the fate of Barron and his group
下场相当惨烈
was more horrifying still.
为什么巴伦没什么变？
Why didn't Barron turn into one?
他变了
He did.
可在这之后几年里
But years later...
他发现了可以逆转异常
he found a way to reverse the effects.
变回人类的方法
To regain humanity.
他们变的不老不死，但是以灵人的形式存在
They had become not immortal gods, but Hollows.
危险冷血致命的
Invisible beasts, dangerous...
隐形怪物！
cold-blooded, deadly.
记得我之前提过他们袭击时间圈吗？
Remember I told you they raided loops?
这就是原因
This is why.
巴伦发现食用其他异能人
Barron discovered that by consuming
特别是儿童期的
the eyes of other peculiars...
异能人的眼睛
especially children...
可以令他恢复
he began to change.
食用到足够多的眼睛，灵人就能
Consume enough, and a Hollow
完全变回人形
can fully regain its human form.
祝各位好胃口
Bon appetit.
只有巴伦和他的同伙能够复原
Just as Barron and some of his friends did.
其他还是以灵人的形态存在
The rest of them are stuck as Hollows.
你是说巴伦吃了我爷爷的
Are you saying that Barron ate my grand...
他自己已经不需要吃眼睛来维持形态了
He needs no more eyes himself.
恐怕是他指使灵人找到了你爷爷，吃了他的眼睛
But I fear he led a Hollow to your grandfather. Yes.
在他们第一次袭击了时间圈后
After the first attacks on loops...
我们也开始更加注意隐蔽，建立新的时间圈
we all got better at hiding, making new loops,
隐匿我们的行踪
keeping our whereabouts secret.
而那些灵人变得越来越贪婪
The Hollows grow more desperate every year...
巴伦则希望能壮大自己的队伍
and Barron wishes to help his friends.
佩小姐！快来！艾娃塞小姐醒了
Miss Peregrine, come quickly. Miss Avocet's awake.
突然，我又飞了进去
And suddenly, I flew into it again...
什么都看不见
Bang! Bang! I couldn't see anything.
佩小姐！他们发现了我新建的时间圈
Oh, Miss Peregrine. They found my new loop.
孩子们，我想尽一切办法试图救下她们
The children. I tried to save them...
但是灵人实在是太多了
but there were so many Hollows.
我都不记得我是怎么逃出来的
I don't know how I escaped.
你现在安全了
You're safe now.
我们不可能安全的
None of us are safe.
他们在我的时间圈里面安了装置
They set up the machine in my loop.
装置就在黑潭塔的地下室
They put it in the cellars at Blackpool Tower.
那些人还在那儿
They're still there.
装置？试验用的
Their machine? The experiment.
他们打算再做一次试验！
They intend to do it again.
这次他将使用更多的回时鸟
This time, he's using more Ymbrynes.
他还是想获得永生
He still wants to be immortal.
Do Hollows only attack peculiars?
当然不是！
Of course not.
他们就是野兽，杰克
They're monsters, Jake.
他们会将眼前的一切都屠杀殆尽
They'll slaughter anything in their path.
岛上有些羊群被杀了
Some sheep on the island were killed.
他们不会已经到了这里吧？
You don't think they're here already, do you?
你有看到长着白色眼睛的人吗？
Have you seen anyone with white eyes?
孩子们，很抱歉，我们不能继续住在这儿了
I'm sorry, children. We can't remain here.
什么？
What?
我们乘坐明早第一班渡船离开这里
We'll leave on the first ferry off the island tomorrow.
回去收拾行李
Pack anything of importance.
我去做些三明治然后哄你们上床睡觉
Then it's sandwiches and early to bed.
离开就再也不会来了吗？
Are we leaving for good?
我们什么时候再回来？不会再回来了
When are we coming back? Never.
如果佩小姐明天晚上
If Miss Peregrine's not here
不重置时间圈
to reset the loop tomorrow night...
这房子就彻底被炸毁了
the house gets bombed.
什么？我们的房子？
But our house.
别哭
Don't cry.
佩小姐会给你们
Miss Peregrine will find you
重新找一座漂亮房子的
another lovely house, somewhere else.
一旦这个时间圈关闭
Once this loop closes, that's it.
我就再也不能回到自己的时空了
I can't get back to my own time.
你在那里过得也不是很开心啊
You didn't seem very happy there.
我不能就这么走了！我还有家人
I can't just leave! I have a family!
你一直觉得自己平凡
And you felt ordinary.
觉得自己什么都不能改变
Like, nothing you do changes anything!
现在你有一个机会
Now you have a chance to do something
可以拯救世界
that changes everything!
杰克，我们现在有危险
Jake, we're in danger.
而你是我们中唯一一个可以看见灵人的
And you're the only one who can see the Hollows.
是，我确实可以看见他们，但是我不是我爷爷
Yeah, see them, sure. But I'm not my grandpa!
我不是，我不知道怎么去战斗
I'm not, and I can't fight.
我不会杀人
I can't kill somebody.
只有一个理由可以让我留下来
There's only one reason that I'd stay here...
别说了！
Please.
你走吧
Just go.
杰克，杰克原来你在这儿！
Jake? Jakey, there you are.
谢天谢地！
Thank God!
听他们说找到了一具尸体时吓死我了
When I heard they found a body, I freaked.
这儿也有流浪狗吗？
Are there stray dogs around here?
你说什么？
What you talking about?
我是说
It's like...
流浪狗发现受伤的动物后
when they find an injured animal,
会先吃掉其中的软组织
they go for the soft parts first.
我父亲去世的时候也是这样
Same thing happened to my father.
警察已经快到了
The police are on their way.
爸爸，我得走了
Look, Dad. I've gotta go.
不行，你那儿也不能去，杰克
What? No. You don't, Jake.
如果这不是意外
If this wasn't an accident,
那就是这个岛上有个疯子
there's a lunatic on the island.
我认识这个岛上的每一个人
I've known everyone on this island my whole life.
除了你和他
Except you, and him.
而他在酒吧里坐了一下午
And he's been in the pub all afternoon.
我也是，我一直都在睡觉
So have I. I was sleeping.
那个盲人呢？
What about the blind fellow?
我以为他也是个盲人
I assumed he was blind.
一个戴墨镜的先生
Gentleman with the dark glasses...
是和我同一天坐渡轮一起过来的
arrived on the same ferry as me?
我总能看见他在这附近
I kept seeing him around.
杰克！
Jake!
杰克，等等！
Jake! Wait!
你儿子还好吧？
Is your son all right?
不好
No.
他有心理障碍
He has mental health issues.
我追不上
I can't go.
我帮你追，我经常会来个5公里跑
Let me. I run 5-Ks all the time.
你好！
Hello?
你好？
是你吗，年轻人？
Is that you, young man?
你能进入？
You came through...
你是个异能人？
You're peculiar?
是的
Oh, yes.
真是多亏了你
And I'm extremely grateful to you.
这些日子想要找到时间圈越来越难了
Terribly hard to find loops these days.
你故意从海滩那儿一直尾随我？
So, you followed me from the beach on purpose?
不不不
Oh, no.
我在很早以前就已经开始关注你了！
I've been following you much further than that.
格兰医生？
Doctor Golan?
有时候
Sometimes.
合适的时候
When it suits me.
一般来说能够局限我异能变化的
The breadth of my peculiarity...
只有我的想象力
is purely limited by my imagination.
只有一样我没有办法改变
The only thing I can't change...
就是我的眼睛
is my eyes.
我是巴伦先生，你好吗？
Mr. Barron. How do you do?
我在你爷爷家见过你
I saw you at your grandfather's.
我本打算从他那儿
I was hoping to get
得到佩小姐的地址
Miss Peregrine's address from him.
但是和我一起过来的旅伴
But, alas, my traveling companion
先我一步找到了他
got to him before I did.
如你所知
As you know...
没什么能阻止饥饿的灵人捕食
there's just no stopping a hungry Hollowgast!
说到我那个同伴
Speaking of my traveling companion...
他已经在来的路上了
he's coming.
劝你还是相信我说的
Believe me when I say to you...
当他到这儿之后
you don't want to be here...
你绝对不会想留下来了
when he arrives.
我们继续往前走吧
So, let's be on our way.
请吧
Shall we?
借过
Excuse me.
等等我
Wait for me.
日历必须要拿上
I mustn't forget our calendar.
能帮我去客厅拿一下吗
Could you fetch it from the parlor
艾娃塞小姐？
please, Miss Avocet?
去帮助其他人吧
Go and help the others.
佩小姐
Miss Peregrine, what a pleasure
终于有机会见到你了！
to meet you at last!
我们能进来吗？
May we come in?
孩子们
Children!
你们都下来吧
Would you make your way down the stairs, please?
巴伦先生！这座房子里轮不到你来下命令
I give the orders in this house, Mr. Barron.
今天不行
Not today.
杰克已经完成他的任务
You should know that Jake has served his purpose.
如果你们还想保他的命，我建议
If you value his life, I suggest
听我的！
everyone does as they're told.
- 孩子们！
- 嘘！
Children! Shush!
没人可以命令他们
No one tells my children what to do!
孩子们
Children...
都下楼到这里来吧
come down here, please.
佩小姐
Miss Peregrine...
我说过让你安静！
I thought I told you to be quiet.
孩子们
Children...
为了杰克的安全
for Jake's safety...
我们现在要按巴伦先生说的做
we're going to do what Mr. Barron asks.
他希望我
He wishes to take me with him
跟他一起去黑池
to his rendezvous in Blackpool.
为了保护自己
So, for his protection...
他希望我变成鸟的样子
he'd like me to assume bird form,
最好是在笼子里
preferably caged.
他还想把你们也全部锁起来
He'd like you to make your way into a lockable room,
比如客厅
such as the parlor...
如果令他感到
as he won't release Jake if he fears
有一丝的不安全
an attack could be mounted upon him...
他都不会放杰克走
once he loses his leverage.
是这样么，巴伦先生？
Correct, Mr. Barron?
你准备牺牲自己和我们
You're sacrificing yourself and all of us...
仅仅为了救杰克？
for Jake?
巴伦先生带着一只空灵，伊诺克
Mr. Barron travels with a Hollow, Enoch.
它一旦来这里，我们都得死
Once it arrives here, we're all dead.
伊诺克，只有杰克能看到空灵们
Enoch. Only Jake can see them.
他是我们唯一的希望
She means he's our only hope.
能照顾你们
It's been my privilege...
是我的荣幸
to care for you all.
再见！孩子们
Goodbye, my children.
你现在可以放开他了
Now let him go.
杰克，答应我
Promise me one thing, Jake.
你会尽力照顾他们所有人
That you will try to look after them all.
我答应你
I promise.
天要黑了
It's getting dark.
到时候连它们的影子都看不到了
You won't even be able to see their shadows.
我们必须待在房子里
We have to stay inside.
这样我们或许还有一丝生机
It's the only place we stand a chance.
他说的对，佩小姐平时
He's quite right. Now, where does
都把武器放在哪里？
Miss Peregrine keep her weapon?
这边，跟我来
In there. Let's go.
孩子们
Now, all right, children.
去把每一扇门窗
Make sure all the doors are locked,
都关好，锁好
and the windows are latched.
全都牢牢关好，快去
Everything must be sealed up tight. Now quickly.
快去！
Quickly! Go!
这儿
Here.
杰克，最好你去接
Jake, I think tonight, you better answer that.
好
Okay.
喂？
Hello?
你好，我是亚伯
Hello, this is Abe.
你是哪位？
Who's that?
你…你不认识我，我是杰克
You don't know me yet. I'm Jake.
哦，你是新来的，欢迎来到这个大家庭，杰克
Ah, you're new. Welcome to the family, Jake.
我不能讲太久
Now, I can't talk long...
帮我告诉佩小姐
so just tell Miss Peregrine...
我在空军基地，我一切都好
I'm at the air base, and I'm fine.
我想告诉你，我很想你
I just wanted to say that I miss you...
如果我让你失望了
and if I disappointed you...
对不起
I'm sorry.
还有，你是世界上最好的爷爷
You're the best grandpa in the world.
菲奥娜！
Fiona. Got it.
艾维赛小姐！
Miss Avocet.
孩子们
Now, children.
有几条命令大家要记住
Now that you're all here, there's a few rules.
你们一定要保证自己的安全
Your primary job is to stay safe.
空灵留着我来对付
Leave the Hollow to me.
千万不要逞英雄
I don't want to see any heroics.
拿着农具的孩子，要记住
Now those of you with garden tools...
你们…
I must insist that you...
不，伊诺克！回来！
No, Enoch. Get back!
快跑！去阁楼
Go. Get to the attic!
接着她！
Take her.
走！走！
Go. Get out!
奥利芙，快走！
Olive, come on!
糟了！要到重置时间了
Crap! It's almost reset!
菲奥娜，你能让那棵树长过来么？
Fiona, is there anything you can do with that tree?
小心点！
Be careful.
我们从这边窗户出去
We're going through the windows.
快走，快一点！
Let's go! Quickly!
过来！
Come on!
克莱尔！快下来
Claire, come on down.
小心点
Be careful.
菲奥娜，快走！
Go, Fiona!
快跑！
Let's go!
- 怎么回事？
- 时间圈关闭了
- Was that...
- The loop closing.
全都没了
It's gone.
对不起，杰克
I'm sorry, Jake.
我们现在怎么办？
What do we do now?
有没有巴伦和佩小姐的踪迹？
Is there any sign of Barron and Miss Peregrine?
他们走了，巴伦一定是乘船走了
Gone. Barron must have had a boat.
我们必须去找他们
We have to go after them.
至少我们知道他们要去黑池
We know he's taking her to Blackpool.
黑池离这儿那么远
But Blackpool is miles away.
况且下一班船要再等好几个小时
The next ferry doesn't go for hours.
我们来不及了
We'll never make it in time.
除非我们现在就有条船！
Not unless we go by boat, too.
在黑池这里有一个时间圈
So, there's a loop here in Blackpool.
只有六个月，是2016年1月11号
It's only six months old. January 11th, 2016.
但现在艾维赛小姐不在了，这个时间圈就无法维持
With Miss Avocet gone, it can't be reset.
时间圈会关闭么？
Won't the loop close?
它就会回到现实时间
Then it's back to real time.
杰克，你知道这意味什么么？
Jake, you know what this means, don't you?
你会死
You're gonna die.
我不是这个意思
That's not what I mean.
我们需要回到自己的时间里
We have to get to our own time,
但你不用
but you don't.
你可以继续生活在2016年
You can continue to live in 2016.
为什么？
But why would I do that?
如果我们杀死巴伦
If we kill Barron...
他死了，时间会继续向前
he'll be gone, but time will carry on.
他就不会去佛罗里达
He won't go to Florida...
亚伯不会死，你也可以回家了
Abe won't die, and you can go home.
我能看到爷爷了
I could see my grandpa.
我可以向他们解释发生的所有事情！
Listen, I can explain everything to them.
我可以让他们再带我回到岛上
I can persuade them to take me to the island and...
你们还会在那里么？
Wait, will you still be there?
我们的旧时间圈永远结束了
Our old loop's gone for good.
我们不会再见的
We wouldn't see each other again.
我以为你想让我留下来
I thought you wanted me to stay.
我知道你更想见到亚伯
I know you'll choose Abe.
如果我真想你留下，就不会告诉你这些了
If I minded, I wouldn't have told you
找到艾维赛小姐的
So, have you found Miss Avocet's
时间圈了么？
loop on the map yet?
在这里，是新建的
It's here. But it's new.
是今年初刚建立的
She made it early this year. That's my year.
如果我们不能在时间圈关闭前出来
If we don't get out before it closes,
我们都要被困在2016年1月了
we're stuck in January 2016.
很好！
Great.
我们全都被时间困住
Time catches up with all of us,
都会死，除了你！有什么计划么？
we all die, except you. Plan?
时间圈在4:30关闭
The loop closes at 4:30.
我们需要抓紧进入时间圈
That means we need to get in,
救出回时鸟，然后尽快出来
rescue the Ymbrynes and then get out.
前提是我们还活着
Yeah, if we're not already dead.
艾维赛小姐说过机器
Miss Avocet said the machine is in the cellar
在黑池塔的地窖里
of the Blackpool Tower building.
也就是说我们要跟空灵面对面
That means we will be indoors... with Hollows.
不…不需要！我有一个计划
No, we won't. I've got a plan.
但我需要你们的帮助
But I'm gonna need your help.
不会是这里吧？
This can't be it, can it?
任何地方都可能是时间圈入口？
Loop entrances can be anywhere.
在伦敦的入口是一个地铁隧道
The one in London's in a subway tunnel.
你确定是这个？
Are you sure this is it?
我觉得是
I think so.
米拉德，我现在需要你…
Millard, there's something I need you to do first.
我知道
All right. I know.
看！那就是黑池塔，不远
Look. There's the tower. It's not far.
说得简单！我可冻死了
Easy for you to say. I'm freezing.
准备好了么？
Ready?
所有通往地窖的通道都被封了
All of the doors to the cellar are locked.
唯一能找到回时鸟的路就是那里
The only way to reach the Ymbrynes is through there.
就是通过那个后台
It's backstage.
你能看到多少个空灵
How many Hollows can you see?
4个，算是个好消息
Four. That's good news.
咱俩对好消息的
I think you and I have
定义可不同
very different definition of good news.
这也就意味着巴伦的其他朋友还没到…
It means Barron's other friends haven't arrived yet.
他们还没开始做实验
So they haven't started the experiment.
所以我们还不晚
We're not too late.
艾玛
Okay, Emma.
你好了么？你知道要说什么
You ready? You know what to say.
杰克
Here, Jake.
其他兄弟马上就会来加入我们
Our brethren should be joining us momentarily.
今天是个…
This is a day to...
下面的听着
You down there!
巴伦先生，我们杀了你的空灵兄弟
We killed your Hollow friend, Mr. Barron.
现在我们来救佩小姐了
And now we've come for Miss Peregrine.
五分钟内带着佩瑞格林小姐
Bring her and all the other Ymbrynes
和其他的回时鸟去码头
to the end of the pier in five minutes...
不然有你好看的
or face the consequences.
这些孩子们一定是
These children must be
像他们的校长一样疯了
as insane as their headmistress.
空灵们可是很喜欢饱餐一顿呢
Still, the Hollows will be glad of a feed.
你们在哪儿呢？
Where are you?
我知道你们在这儿
I know you're in here somewhere!
听着
Good. Listen to me.
我要你们跟着阿彻先生和克拉克先生
I want you to follow Mr. Archer and Mr. Clark.
他们会带你们去码头
They're going to take you down to the pier...
吃个下午茶
for a little afternoon tea.
阿彻先生，克拉克先生
Mr. Archer, Mr. Clark...
请带着空灵们去码头吧
gather the Hollows and take them to the pier.
这几个孩子杀了马尔萨斯？
Those children killed Malthus?
自从马尔萨斯杀了亚伯·波特曼
Barron's had it in for Malthus
巴伦先生就想干掉他
ever since he killed Abe Portman.
我跟踪了他好几个月
I tracked Abe Portman for months.
我当时只需要几分钟
All I needed was a few minutes...
来问出佩小姐的时间圈地址
to get the location of Miss Peregrine's loop from him.
但是不行
But no!
马尔萨斯等不及
Malthus couldn't wait.
所以呢
Instead...
我就必须得在那
I had to masquerade as a psychiatrist...
待上三个星期
for three weeks...
伪装成心理医生
in Florida!
你去过佛罗里达么？
Have you ever been to Florida?
我不是让你们带着空灵们去码头？
Did I not tell you to gather the Hollows?
万一是个陷阱怎么办
What if it's a trap?
爱德华小姐，肯定是个陷阱咯，但那又怎样？
Of course, it is, Miss Edwards. But what of it?
几个小屁孩对空灵就是自寻死路
A couple of children against four Hollows.
赶紧行动啊
Let's get this over with.
杰克，我被电线卡住了
Jake, I'm stuck!
快！
Hurry up!
小心
Watch out!
他们来了！
They're coming!
快走
Let's go.
就现在伊诺克！
Enoch. Now!
动手！
Go! Now!
可以看见了
Starting to see them now.
第二步
Phase two.
艾玛！快！
Emma, go.
别傻站在这儿！去抓住他们！
Don't just stand there. Get them!
干得好，孩子们，可以开始第二步计划了
All right. Good job, guys. It's time for step two.
救出佩瑞格林小姐
Save Miss Peregrine!
呃…那算是第三步
That's sort of step three.
在这之前我们得先把巴伦解决了
First, we've got to deal with Barron.
他们现在该回来了
They should've been back by now.
我就说是个陷阱
I said it was a trap.
如果真是这样
If that's true...
我们要转移回时鸟了
perhaps we should move the Ymbrynes now.
你认真的么？
You're not serious?
我看起来像开玩笑的么？
Do I not look serious?
是谁跋山涉水
Do I not look like a man who has searched the globe...
就为了多吃一个眼睛
looking for just one more eye to eat...
多点儿人性
in hopes of regaining sufficient humanity...
好继续他的研究？
to return to his research?
是谁不遗余力花费数年
A man who's spent years hunting Ymbrynes...
抓起这些回时鸟就为了今晚？
in preparation for this night...
整整两…不…三天都待在威尔士
and two, no, three days, in Wales...
装作在观鸟
pretending to look at birds!
我告诉你
I assure you...
我不会傻傻站在这里
I will not stand idly by...
眼看着一切脱离我的计划
to see my destiny derailed.
休，就现在！
Hugh, do it now!
回来！
Come back here!
给我抓住他们！
Get them!
下去！
Go. Get down!
你以为你能阻止我？
You think you can stand in my way?
杰克，如果你没有这点儿异能
You, Jake, content to age and die...
你是不是就满足于生老病死的生活？
as if you had not the gift of peculiarity at all?
我更高级
I am a higher being.
我知道永生的方法
I hold the secret to eternal life!
抱歉，打扰一下
Sorry to interrupt.
什么…
What the...
布朗温
Bronwyn.
杰克，你又没打中
You missed me again, Jake.
我猜射的准肯定不是你的异能吧
I take it accuracy is not your peculiarity.
亚伯比你强多了
Abe was a much worthier adversary.
别让他接近回时鸟！
Don't let him get to the birds.
你可得跟我介绍一下你的裁缝
You must put me in contact with your tailor.
回时鸟…回时鸟…我来啦！
Ymbrynes, Ymbrynes! Here I come!
冰冻
Cold?
直到血液都凝固
Wait till the blood freezes in your veins.
你就打算这么救你朋友？
That was your attempt to rescue your friend, was it?
杰克！
Jake.
我尽量拖住他
I'll hold him off as long as I can.
你什么时候才能明白
When are you going to realize
自己准头有多差？
you are a terrible shot with that thing.
带上其他人，我们在时间圈入口那里见
Get the others. I'll meet you at the loop entrance.
我这就救你出来
Let's get you out.
反正最后
Eventually...
你也会没气可吹
you're going to run out of breath.
窒息而死
And it'll all be over!
为你亲爱的杰克和佩小姐…
Death for your beloved Jake and Miss Peregrine...
还有为了我的永生而死
everlasting life for me!
你该吃点薄荷了
And a mint for you.
奥丽芙！
Olive.
对不起，奥丽芙
I'm so sorry, Olive.
这么多年我都没珍惜你
All these years, I never appreciated you.
我一直不知道自己有多幸运
I didn't see how lucky I was.
我习惯了你一直陪在我身边，从没意识到
I got so used to having you there, I never realized...
没意识到什么？
You never realized what?
找到你们的孩子们，创造新的时间圈
Find your children. Create new loops.
杰克
So, Jake...
原来是继承了你祖父的异能
I see you've inherited your grandfather's peculiarity.
就是像他一样讨厌
You're just as annoying as he was.
说到亚伯
Speaking of Abe...
记得你死后要是看见他
if you should see him in the afterlife...
替我问候他
give him my regards.
不能再让他带走你了
Please. We can't risk him taking you again.
伊诺克！其他人呢？
Enoch! Where are the others?
他们都很安全，奥丽芙正带他们回船上
They're safe. Olive is leading them back to the Ghost Train.
杰克需要我们，巴伦太强了
Jake needs us. Barron's too strong.
你现在没了佩小姐
You've lost Miss Peregrine.
你什么都没了！结束了！
You've lost everything. It's over.
杰克？
Jake?
艾玛？
Emma?
等一下，那不是我，那是巴伦
No, wait. Look. That's not me. It's Barron.
别听他的
Don't listen to him.
他才是巴伦，我是杰克
He's Barron. No, I'm Jake.
他是巴伦
That's Barron.
我比杰克准的多
I've got a better shot than Jake.
你俩最好都给我别动
So, neither of you move until we sort this.
听着，我是杰克
Listen to me. I'm Jake.
我家在佛罗里达，梦想成为探险家
I grew up in Florida and I wanted to be an explorer.
我认为一切都不会改变，因为我很普通
I thought nothing would ever change because I was ordinary.
他是杰克，那是巴伦
That's Jake. Get Barron.
等一下！他是我心理医生
No. Look. I told him all of this.
这些都是我告诉他的
She was my psychiatrist.
你们来对付他，我去找佩小姐
Look, you deal with him. I'll go find Miss Peregrine.
等一下
Wait.
我可以证明自己
Look, I can prove that I'm me...
因为我并不普通
because I'm not ordinary.
我能做的事情别人不行
I can do something no one else can
我能看到那怪物
I can see the monsters.
看看，是我！
No, wait. It's me!
伊诺克！
Enoch!
我们得走了，时间圈要关了
We need to go. The loop is closing.
我们要走了
Those of us who are leaving.
艾玛…
Emma.
你爱你祖父
You love your grandfather.
其他的就不用多说了
There's nothing more to explain.
不，我答应了佩小姐照顾你们
No, I promised Miss Peregrine I'd look after you all.
现在她受伤了，你们也不在时间圈里
And with her injured, and you without a loop...
她会康复的
She'll recover.
到那之前，我们继续生活在1943年
Until then, we'll be in 1943.
只是像普通人一样
We'll only age one day at a time.
经历时间而已
Like normal people.
这也不是什么坏事
Which can be no bad thing.
那空灵怎么办？
What about the Hollows?
只要他们还在，你们就不安全
As long as they're out there, you're not safe.
杰克，没有你我们也能安全
We don't need you to make us feel safe, Jake.
因为你已经教给我们更好的
Because you made us feel brave.
你让我们勇敢
And that's even better.
伙伴们，走吧！
Come on, guys. Let's go.
小老虎
Tygrysku.
之后我们就道别了
And then we said goodbye...
时间圈关闭了
and the loop closed.
我害怕你不在这儿了
I was so scared that you wouldn't be here.
我就再也见不到你了
That I'd never see you again.
我很好
I'm safe.
我要送你生日礼物
Let me give you your birthday present.
爷爷，我的生日还有好几个月呢
Grandpa, my birthday isn't for months.
这是你的路费
For your travels.
杰克，去找她吧
Go to her, Jake.
你有地图
You have the map.
你能回到1943年
You can get back to 1943.
但他们在船上
No. Even so, they took a boat.
我不知道他们现在在哪儿
I don't know where they are.
但你知道他们曾经在哪儿
But you know where they were.
你是不知道我怎么过来的
You have no idea how long it took me to get here.
最近的时间圈在加利福尼亚沙漠
The closest loop was in the California desert.
我从那里去了东京的时间圈
I used it to get to the Tokyo loop.
然后又去了离这儿最近的1942年时间圈
And that led me to the nearest loop back in 1942...
我参加了海军还受伤了
where I wound up joining the Navy.
这就别多问了
Don't ask.
之后我在伦敦待了两个月想要…
Then I spent two months in London trying to...
准备好，加速前进！
Ready for full speed ahead!